zemana.com 2013-12-11

# Zemana AntiLogger - The #1 Privacy Protection Software

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Zemana Ltd. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the [ http://www.zemana.com](http://www.zemana.com/) website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Zemana Ltd..

##  Personal identification information 

We may collect personally identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. 

##  Non-personal identification information 

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. 

##  Web browser cookies 

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. 

##  How we use collected information 

Zemana Ltd. collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes: 

  * \- To personalize user experience

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. 

  * \- To improve our Site

We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you. 

  * \- To improve customer service

Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs. 

  * \- To process transactions

We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service. 

  * \- To send periodic emails

The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site. 

##  How we protect your information 

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. 

##  Sharing your personal information 

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission. 

##  Third party websites 

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies. 

##  IntelliGuard Cloud Data 

By enabling the Zemana Ltd. software, you agree to allow the program to collect and report data to the Zemana IntelliGuard Cloud Infrastructure (hereinafter referred to as IntelliGuard Cloud Data), anonymously and upon certain events. These events are generated by program activity on your computer, which activates a trigger (or policy) within the Zemana Ltd. software. A policy is a rule within the software that monitors areas of your computer system for malicious program activity. 

When an event is triggered, the following data about the suspicious program is transmitted:

  * The action that you apply or that Zemana applies automatically
  * The MD5 sum of the file
  * The digital signature of the file
  * The size of the file
  * Version information of the file

Zemana IntelliGuard also collects standard computer information, which includes information regarding your computer software and hardware, such as your IP address, operating system and version.

The IntelliGuard Cloud Data is anonymous and does not collect and process any personal user information. 

Upon receipt, the IntelliGuard Cloud Data is aggregated into our Zemana Threat Database and used to create rules which will make determinations on “safe” or “malicious” files and programs. In addition, the IntelliGuard Cloud Data is used to produce general statistics on attacks and threats; these statistics may be used by Zemana Ltd. in its malware research, publicity, marketing and promotional materials. 

You can enable and disable IntelliGuard Cloud Data at any time by visiting the General Settings under your Zemana Ltd. software’s Options page. 

The IntelliGuard Cloud Database Service may be subject to occasional downtime for maintenance, repair, upgrade and update. 

##  Changes to this privacy policy 

Zemana Ltd. has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

##  Your acceptance of these terms 

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and  terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

###  Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

##  Contact Information

**Zemana**

Thracian Technology Development Park 48 Aysekadin Yerleskesi  
22030 Edirne / TURKEY 

**Phone**  
Turkey : +90 (284) 988 0160  
USA : +1 (866) 293 2016 

(Please note that we do not offer technical support by phone, only through  our support form.)

**Email :** support@zemana.com
